inquirer.net 2019-11-04

# Privacy Statement - INQUIRER.net Services | INQUIRER.net Services

#### Privacy Statement

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of [www.inquirer.net](http://www.inquirer.net/). It is our continuing goal to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information and user privacy practices.

By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this privacy statement. If you feel that we are not abiding by our posted privacy statement, please send us an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6c0a0909080e0d0f072c05021d19051e091e42020918)

**Collection of Personal Information**

We collect information from our users at several different points on our website.

We collect information about your computer hardware and software such as your IP address, device type, browser type, domain names, time spent, and referring website addresses.

We sometimes collect personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, address or mobile or landline number. We also at times collect anonymous demographic information such as your age, gender, location, browsing behaviour, interests and favorites.

**Use of Personal Information**

Generally, we use personal information to analyze trends, administer the website, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

We also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from us, our affiliates, and partners.

When we hold surveys or promos, we may require users to give their contact information (such as name, email, or residential address or mobile number) and demographic information (such as age, income level, or gender). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest or to inform them if they have won in a certain contest or promo. It is optional for the user to provide a unique identifiers (such as social security number or driver’s license number).

We offer various email services. We require information from the user in order for him or her to avail of such free services. This information is used only as contact information and reference.

We partner with other parties to provide services that allow us to deliver the services uder the website or assist us in measuring key website statistics. When the user signs up for there services, we may be required to share names, or other information that is absolutely necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. In all cases, they are required to keep the information confidential.

**Use of Cookies** **  
****  
** We use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. You are free to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of the website.  
  
Some of our business partners use cookies on our website. For the complete list and the key terms and conditions specifically applicable to each of our partners, please refer to the list in this link. **  
****  
****Security of Personal Information** **  
****  
** We have established security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the personally identifiable information you provide on secured computer servers protected from unlawful access, fraudulent misuse, unlawful destruction, alteration and contamination.   
  
If you have provided us your personal information, you have the right to ask for a copy of any personal information we hold about you, as well as to ask for it to be corrected if you think it is wrong. To do so, please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3f595a5a5b5d5e5c547f56514e4a564d5a4d11515a4b).

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**Revisions of this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Exponential Interactive Privacy Statement**

Subject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time via . For more details including access requests and complaints, review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Don’t miss out on the latest news and information. Follow us: [](https://www.facebook.com/inquirerdotnet) [](https://twitter.com/inquirerdotnet)
